# **Earnest Cheatham**

Ontario, CA

ej\_cheatham@yahoo.com - (951) 588-3805

Respected employee who is trustworthy, hard working and dedicated. Extensive experience in customer service and sales. Self driven to reach challenging revenue goals. Independent decision-making. Able to multitask effectively. Extremely focused on problem areas, minimizing issues and executing competent solutions.

Willing to relocate: Anywhere

Authorized to work in the US for any employer

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

#### **Solar City**

Field Energy Specialist - Corona, CA - April 2014 to Present

Engage customers regarding SolarCity's clean energy solutions. Drive the creation of in store leads to meet personal and team sales goals and objectives. Collaborate with Outside Solar Sales Consultants to confirm in-home appointments. Set up SolarCity displays and collateral

Conduct in-store seminars and events for 20 or more people. Also trained new associates because I'm one of the Top Sales producers. I excellent written and verbal communication skills. Very on-point with my follow through and communication.

#### **Mobile Lead Consultant**

Staples - Mira Loma, CA - April 2013 to February 2014

My main goal was to use the knowledge I knew about mobile technology to sale phones and use outstanding customer service to meet weekly and monthly sales quotas. I have experience with AT&T, T-Mobile, and Verizon carriers. I was top 3 in the region in mobile sales. Sold service plans for other products in the store. Emailed, Filled, and Faxed documents.

#### **Head Cashier**

Home Depot - Anaheim Hills, CA - June 2011 to February 2013

Supervision of the front of the store which includes the cashing operations (front registers, self check-out, returns desk, and garden), front lot, and maintaining a safe and clean working environment. Also used customer service skills making sure that every customer found what they were looking for and making sure that the store's shrink is as minimal as possible. I helped solicit credit cards as well. Lead store in credit cards opened our store was top 2 in region.

#### **Ticket Taker**

Disneyland - Anaheim, CA - July 2009 to September 2009

Direct guest around park Security Screen bags Take Tickets Greet Customers and Assist guest with any questions.

#### Sales Associate

Party City - Chino Hills, CA - October 2007 to November 2008

Greet customers, Assisted Customers with any costume or store product advice

### **EDUCATION**

### **BA in Psychology**

California State University of Los Angeles - Los Angeles, CA 2008 to 2013

## Diploma

Norco High School - Norco, CA 2003 to 2007